

BRANDON SHRADER

Jack of All Trades UI/UX, Modeling, Branding & More.

ABOUT

An unconventional, self-taught 3D Generalist with 7+ years of experience in creative direction between a multitude of diverse mediums. Professionally played eSports for two world renowned gaming organizations, while leading multiple time-sensitive team projects. I'm a charismatic soul with passion for creativity and direction. I can work efficiently alone on multiple projects and/or work effectively with a group of other colleagues.



EXPERIENCE

3YR 2019-Now

3D GENERALIST

Self Employed / Canton, OH

- Attract 1,000+ unique customers in my personal marketplace for products ranging from 3D Models, Props, Ready-to-Use Unity 3D Assets, and PBR Materials & Textures.
- Coordinate with 150+ clients requesting Custom Modeling, Texturing, Rigging, Animation, and Unity 3D Game Logic.
- Conceptualized, Directed and Composed original Character Designs, Environments, and Props for personal projects.

1YR 2019-2020

TEAM LEAD & ESPORTS PLAYER

100 Thieves / Los Angeles, CA

- Lead and organize a team of professionals to a common goal, while solving real time problems along the way. Evaluate their performance and adjust accordingly.
- Plan, concept, and execute real time strategies to overcome obstacles, with myself and my team to obtain a common goal. Document, and professionally produce content around said goal.
- Utilize my abilities to, compete, overcome, and proceed through any obstacles while maintaining a professional brand outlook, and further push this through social media.

6MO 2019-2019

CONTENT CREATOR & ESPORTS PLAYER

Team Liquid / Los Angeles, CA

- Create interactive, entertaining, and engaging content around the brand. Work with other professionals in this aspect to engage an audience and further spread the brand's name and identity.
- Perform at my highest level possible, among other professionals to achieve a common goal. Practice, and refine my skills I have to obtain said goal.



EDUCATION

3.5YR 2016-2019

ADVERTISING & GRAPHIC DESIGN

Columbus College of Art & Design / Columbus, OH

• Completed work towards Bachelor of Arts (B.A) Interactive & Graphic Art. Majored in Advertising & Graphic Design, Minored in Film & Studio Photography.



SKILLS

Blender 3D
Unity 3D
Figma
Rigging
Animation
Product Rendering
Substance Painter
Hardsurface / Organic Modeling
Concept Art
Game Design / Development
Graphic Design
Motion Graphic
Studio & Film Photography
Film Development

Branding & Logo Design
UI / UX Design
Advertising
Marketing
Team Management
Team Direction
Art Direction
Project Management
Entertainment
Content Creation
Videography / Video Editing
Social Media Management







